<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tyron Wytrykowski</title>
    <link>http://example.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Tyron Wytrykowski</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2016 19:41:01 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://example.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>S&amp;P Global</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/sp_global/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2016 19:41:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/sp_global/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I was tasked to rebrand and develop a wide array of S&amp;amp;P Global&amp;rsquo;s marketing materials, ranging from email templates to lead generating landing pages.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JHA Recruitment</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/jha_recruitment/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2016 19:41:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/jha_recruitment/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;JHA Recruitment&amp;rsquo;s website was rebranded and designed and built to meet their growing needs.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pure HTML &amp; CSS Ice-cream</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/html-css_ice-cream/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2016 19:41:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/html-css_ice-cream/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;These are the types of projects I end up creating when learning new techniques.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Get in touch</title>
      <link>http://example.org/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2016 13:00:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/contact/</guid>
      <description>When she reached the first hills of the Italic Mountains, she had a last view back on the skyline of her hometown Bookmarksgrove, the headline of Alphabet Village and the subline of her own road, the Line Lane. Pityful a rethoric question ran over her cheek, then
Effects present letters inquiry no an removed or friends. Desire behind latter me though in. Supposing shameless am he engrossed up additions. My possible peculiar together to.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resume</title>
      <link>http://example.org/resume/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/resume/</guid>
      <description>I enjoy all things digital. If I am not building websites and learning new things, I am tinkering away on my 3d printer and making things. With a strong background in design, I enjoy bringing creativity in to my development process and always passionate to learn more along the way.
Experience Situation Publishing (The Register) Front end Developer | December 2017 — Present  Develop and design of responsive HTML, CSS, &amp;amp; JS landing page templates, to be reused within in the companies CRM for a wide range of client facing marketing campaigns and build and development of HTML responsive lead generation pages.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>